[Music]
so I wasn't afraid about dying or having
cancer or or being sick but all the
thoughts rushing into my head was my son
what am i leaving behind for him you
know who's going to take care of him if
something happens to me how is he going
to take in my son my future his future
did I prepare for this do I have
anything saved for him like who's going
to take care of him and it's going to
scar him for life it's going to how it's
going to affect him you need to think
about the people you love prepare for
the people you know so really it wasn't
about this or having cancer it was the
thoughts of how am I going to take care
of the people I love when I'm gone
[Music]